Search [Notifications](https://www.fakku.net/notifications) [Cart](https://www.fakku.net/cart)

Search 

[Our Summer Sale](https://www.fakku.net/sale/summer-sale-2024) is still running until the 14th - up to 80% off on over 2000 digital titles!

Hide Notice

Privacy Policy
==============

Last Modified: May 24th, 2018

This Privacy Policy governs each website (the “Sites”), mobile site, application and/or other service provided (collectively, the “Service(s)”) by FAKKU, LLC (“we,” “us” or “our”). This Privacy Policy sets forth our policy with respect to information that is collected from visitors to the Site and users of the Services (“you”). Under applicable law, FAKKU, LLC. is the “data controller” of personal data collected through the Services.

What You’re Consenting To
-------------------------

By using, or interacting, with the Services, you are consenting to the following:

* The use of cookies and other technologies;
* The transfer of your information outside of the country where you live;
* The collection, use, sharing, and other processing of your information, including for advertising and notification-related purposes;
* The public availability of your information (e.g., the username on your profile) and the controls over such information.

Information We Collection
-------------------------

When you interact with us through the Services, we may collection information from you, as described below:

### Information You Provide

When you register for access to the Services, or use certain Services, we may collect information such as but not limited to username, email address, password, address, postal code, and country.

### Information We Automatically Collect

When you visit the Services, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including but not limited to information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Services, we collect information about the individual web pages that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Services, and information about how you interact with the Services.

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. We use cookies and similar technologies to keep track of which account you have logged into and for notification settings.

We also use third party analytic tools, such as Google Analytics, on our Services that employ cookies to collection information concerning your use of the Services.

Many web browsers allow you to manage your preferences. You can set your browser preferences to refuse cookies or delete certain cookies. For more information about cookies, please visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Please note, if you choose to block cookies, doing so may impair the Services or prevent certain aspects of it from functioning.

### Pixel Tags

We use other similar technologies such as Pixel Tags (transparent graphic images place on a page or in an email) to indicate that a page or email has been viewed by you.

By accepting this Privacy Policy, you hereby consent to the use of the cookies and other technologies as described above.

How We Use Your Information
---------------------------

### Use of Service

We use your information to provide, personalise, and improve your experience with the Services and to ensure the technical functionality of the Service.

### Research & Statistics

In an effort to better understand and improve the Services for our users, we may conduct research on our user demographics, interests and behavior based on the information we collect. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and we may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to third parties for other lawful purposes.

### Customer Orders & Payments

We use the Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Services (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

* Communicate with you;
* Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
* When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

### Marketing & Notifications

We may use your information to communicate with you directly for marketing and promotional purposes via emails, notifications, or other messages, in accordance with any permissions you may communicated to us through your account settings.

Sharing Information
-------------------

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site -- you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

Security
--------

We take reasonable data protection precautions in an effort to safeguard, and help prevent, against unauthorized access to the information we collect. However, no security measure is ever fully secure or error free, therefore we do not, and cannot, guarantee the security of user information.

Your Rights and Choices
-----------------------

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Service), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

Do Not Track
------------

Due to there being no accepted standard on how to respond, please note that we do not alter our Service’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

Data Retention
--------------

When interacting with the Services, including when submitting a Payment or Order, we will maintain your Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

Children
--------

Our Services are strictly limited to adults 18 years of age and over. If you do not meet this criteria, you are strictly forbidden from accessing, or viewing the contents of the Services. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information, or data, from any persons who have not met this age criteria.

Changes To This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Please review this policy occasionally, especially before you provide any information. This Privacy Policy was last modified on the date indicated at the beginning of the policy.

Your continued use of the Services after any changes to this Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to continue using the Services under the new revised Privacy Policy, you may terminate the agreement by contacting us through the contact information below.

Contacting Us
-------------

Please feel free to contact us if you have any question about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Services. You may contact us either via our [Contact Form](https://www.fakku.net/contact) or via contact@fakku.net.

FAKKU, LLC.  
\[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer\]  
PO Box 9009  
Portland, OR 97207  
United States

Popular Tags Today:

© FAKKU, LLC 2024 All rights reserved.

Close sidebar [Notifications](https://www.fakku.net/notifications) Dark mode
